**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

#### > SYNOPSIS

4 years of IT experience in Functional Testing and Non-Functional Testing – **Automation** (Selenium WebDriver), Manual **& Quality Assurance**. Seeking a challenging and exciting career where currency are ideas, smart work with rigorous thinking and boundless curiosity.

### > AREAS of EXPERTISE

| E2E Manual Testing - Web applications,     Mobile App Testing | <ul> <li>Automation – Web Applications (Selenium WebDriver)</li> </ul> |
|---|--|
| Test Data Preparation – Web / Mobile                          | Test / Defect reporting and management                                 |

### > TECHNICAL SKILLS

| Tools            | Selenium WebDriver, PyCharm, Bitbucket             |
|------------------|--|
| Other Tools      | Eclipse, Jira, qTest                               |
| Frameworks       | TestNG, Data Driven Development, Page Object Model |
| Languages known  | Java, SQL  |
| Functional Area  | Core Banking, Hospitality                          |
| Operating System | Windows / iOS / Android                            |

# **EDUCATION**

 Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology
 R. C. Patel Institute of Technology – Shirpur, Maharashtra Bachelor's degree with aggregate 62.90 % in year 2017

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

# > CERTIFICATION SUMMARY

• Completed Selenium Advanced Automation Tester Certification (Infosys Limited)

• Diploma in Software Testing (SEED InfoTech)

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

| Infosys Limited, Pune Designation: Test Engineer                   |   |  |
|--|---|--|
| Current Project: Ally Bank – Banking domain (Apr 2021 – till date) |   |  |
| Technology Stack   | Manual Testing, Python, Mobile Automation, Bitbucket  |  |
| Responsibilities   | <ul> <li>Execute test cases manually at the time of Regression Testing</li> <li>Identify candidate for automation Testcases and develop the test scripts.</li> <li>Automated test scripts for different platforms like iOS, Android</li> <li>Updating the code in repository using bitbucket</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification</li> <li>Contributed into other teams for UI validation</li> </ul> |  |

| INNsight Interactive, Mumbai Designation: QA Analyst               |  |  |
|--|--|--|
| Previous Project: Hospitality domain project (Sep 2019 – Apr 2021) |  |  |
| Technology Stack   | Manual Testing, Selenium, Java, Web Automation   |  |
| Responsibilities   | <ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement specifications</li> <li>Identify and write the test cases in excel</li> <li>Manual Test case execution on web and mobile application</li> <li>Automated test scripts for Web application and websites, using Selenium WebDriver</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification</li> </ul> |  |

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

| Synastute Software, Nashik Designation: QA Engineer     |   |  |
|---|---|--|
| Previous Project: Seller Overview (Sep 2018 – Aug 2019) |   |  |
| Technology Stack  | Manual Testing, Selenium, Java, Web Automation  |  |
| Responsibilities:                                       | <ul> <li>Execute test cases manually</li> <li>Automated test scripts for Web application, using Selenium WebDriver</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification</li> <li>Collect and track daily test execution metrics and provide status report</li> </ul> |  |

| Synastute Software, Nashik Designation: QA Engineer     |   |  |
|---|---|--|
| Previous Project: Somers Crossing (Dec 2017 – Sep 2018) |   |  |
| Technology Stack  | Manual testing  |  |
| Responsibilities:                                       | <ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional RequirementSpecification</li> <li>Identify and write the test scenarios and test cases in Excel.</li> <li>Execute test cases manually</li> <li>Identify defect.</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification.</li> <li>Collect and track daily test execution metrics and provide status report</li> </ul> |  |

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

### > STRENGTHS

- Capable of Quick learning and delivering solutions as an individual and as part of a team
- Good analytical skills, presentation skills with good communication skills
- self-starter and consistent performer
- Result oriented, self-driven, highly motivated, smart, and hungry to learn new technologies, methodologies, strategies, and processes.

#### > PERSONAL INFORMATION

Marital Status: Unmarried
 Hobbies: Singing, Dancing
 Date of birth: 16<sup>th</sup> May 1995

• Permanent address: Khanderao Pada, Thalner, Tal: Shirpur, Dist: Dhule, 425421